the following content is provided under a Creative Commons license
以下内容是根据Creative Commons授权提供
your support will help MIT OpenCourseWare continue to offer
您的支持将有助于麻省理工学院开放式课程继续报价
high-quality educational resources for free
免费优质教育资源
to make a donation or view additional materials from hundreds of them IT
进行捐赠或查看附加材料由数百人资讯
courses
课程
visit MIT OpenCourseWare at 0 CW
参观麻省理工学院开放式课程在0 CW
that MIT that EDU home
麻省理工学院的EDU家
the
该
the new the last time
新的最后一次
we began the development love the discrete-time
我们开始发展爱情的离散时间
for EA transform and
对EA变换和
just days with the continuous-time case we first
与连续时间情况下，仅仅几天我们首先
treated the notion a periodic signals this led to the forty a series
治疗的概念一个周期信号，这导致了40系列
and then we generalize that to the Fourier transform
然后我们推广的傅里叶变换
and finally incorporated within the framework for the four th
和为4个的范围内最终并入
transform both a periodic and periodic signals
改造既有周期性和周期信号
in today's lecture but I'd like to do
在今天的讲座，但是我想要做的
is expand on some other properties
是扩大了一些其他属性
love for EA transform and indicate how those properties are used for a variety
爱对EA变换，并指出如何将这些属性用于各种
of things
事
well let's begin by reviewing the Fourier transform
好，让我们首先回顾了傅立叶变换
as we develop did last time it of course involves
当然，我们开发并最后一次涉及
a synthesis equation and and analysis equation
合成公式，并分析方程
the synthesis equation expressing X a van
表示X中的面包车合成公式
the sequence in terms of the Fourier transform
在傅里叶变换计算的顺序
any analysis equation telling us how to obtain
任何分析方程告诉我们如何获得
the Fourier transform from the original sequence
从原始序列的傅立叶变换
and I draw your attention again to
我再次提请你注意
the basic point that the synthesis equation
基本点的合成公式
essentially corresponds to decomposing
基本上对应于分解
the sequence as a linear combination
该序列作为一个线性组合
of complex exponentials with amplitude said are in effect
复指数振幅说是效果
proportional to the 48 transport now
正比于48运输现
in the discrete-time Fourier transform just as the continuous-time
在离散时间傅里叶变换只是作为连续时间
for a transform has a number all
对于一个变换有许多都
important and useful properties of course
当然重要和有用的性质
as i stress last time it's a function 0
我强调最后一次它是一个功能0
a continuous variable and it's also a complex-valued function
连续变量和它也是一个复值函数
which means dead when we represented in general
这意味着死亡，当我们代表一般
requires a representation in terms of its
需要在方面有代表性
real part an imaginary part or in terms of magnitude and angle
实部的幅度和角度的一个虚部，或
also as i indicated last time
也正如我最后一次
the Fourier transform is
傅立叶变换是
a periodic function of frequency
频率的周期函数
and the periodicity is
和周期性
with a period up to par i and
与一期达到标准i和
so it says in effect dead the Fourier transform if we replace the frequency
所以说，实际上死的傅里叶变换，如果我们更换频率
variable
变量
by an integer multiple to pie
由整数倍来馅饼
the function repeats and I stress again
该功能重复，我再次强调
that the underlying basis
底层基础
for this periodicity property is the fact
这种周期性的属性是事实
that its the setup complex exponentials
其设置复指数
that are inherently periodic in frequency
这本质上是周期性的频率
and so of course any representation using them would
所以当然任何声明使用它们会
in effect generate a
实际上生成
periodicity with this period of two pi
周期性与此为期PI
just an is
只是一个是
in continuous-time the Fourier transform has
在连续时间傅里叶变换具有
important symmetry properties and in particular
重要的对称特性，特别是
if the sequence x7 is
如果序列X7是
real value an the 4e
真正的价值的4E
transform is conjugate symmetric
变换是共轭对称
in other words if we replace Omega by minus Omega
换句话说，如果我们取代了欧米茄欧米茄负
that's equivalent to applying complex conjugation to the 48 transport and
这相当于应用复共轭到48运输和
as a cock consequence this conjugate symmetry
作为一只公鸡这个结果共轭对称性
this results in asymmetry
这导致不对称
in the real part that is an even symmetry
中的实数部分是一个偶对称
or the magnitude has an even symmetry
或幅度具有均匀的对称性
whereas the imaginary part or the phase angle
而虚部或相位角
is are are both art summit and these are symmetry properties again
IS的都是艺术峰会，这些都是对称特性再次
that are identical to the symmetry properties that we saw in
这是相同的，我们在看到了对称性质
continuous-time
连续时间
well let's see this in the context I'll an example that we worked last time and
那么让我们来看看这在方面，我会说我们的工作上次的例子，
that
那
will want to draw attention to
将要提请注意
in reference to several issues is this lecture goes along
在提到的几个问题是这次讲座随之而来
and that is the Fourier transform all
那就是傅立叶变换所有
a real damp expanding exponential
一个真正受潮膨胀指数
so the sequence that we
这样的顺序，我们
are talking about is a to the end you have an
谈的是一个到最后你有一个
and let's consider a to be positive
让我们考虑一个是积极的
we saw last time that the Fourier transform from the for this sequence
我们看到最后一次傅里叶从变换顺序
algebraically is up this form
代数是此表
and if we look at its magnitude and angle
如果我们看一下它的大小和角度
the magnet to I show here
磁铁来我这里展示
and the magnitude as we see has the properties that we indicated
和我们看到的幅度具有我们所表示的性质
is and even function of frequency
是与频率的偶函数
course it's a function of a continuous variable
当然，这是一个连续变量的函数
and it in addition is periodic
它除了是周期性的
with a period of two part
用了一段两部分
on the other hand if we look at the phase angle below it
在另一方面，如果我们看看它下面的相位角
the phase angle has a symmetry which is ought symmetric
相位角具有对称性这是应该对称
and that's indicated clearly in this picture
而这清楚地表明了在这张照片
and of course in addition to being eyed symmetric it naturally has to be
当然除了是眼睛的对称它自然必须
again a periodic function of frequency
频率的再一个周期函数
with the period up to par
以期达到标准
okay so we have some symmetry properties we have this inherent periodicity in the
好了，我们有我们这种固有的周期性在一些对称性质
48 transform which
48的变换
arms stressing very heavily because it forms
武器强调非常沉重，因为它形成
the basic difference between continuous-time and discrete-time
连续时间和离散时间之间的基本区别
in addition to these properties have the four EA transform
除了这些属性有四个EA变换
there are a number of other properties
还有一些其它性质
day are particularly useful in
每天都在特别有用
the manipulation of the 48 transform and in fact
在48的操作变换和实际上
using the Fourier transform to for example
使用傅立叶变换，例如
an ally systems represented by when you're past the coefficient difference
当你过去系数差所代表的盟友系统
equations
方程
bear in the text is a
熊在文中是一个
longer list the properties but let me just draw your attention
不再列出的属性，但我只想提请您注意
to several of them one
几个其中之一
is the time shifting property
是时移特性
and the time shifting property tells us dead
和时移特性告诉我们死
if Xserve Omega is the Fourier transform
如果Xserve的欧米茄是傅立叶变换
objective and then the Fourier transform
目标，然后将傅立叶变换
are x7 shifted in time
在时间上X7转移
is that same for EA transform multiplied by
是相同的EA变换乘以
this factor which is a with your face fact
这个因素是一个与你的脸其实
so time-shifting introduces
因此时移介绍
a linear phase turn and by the way I recall
线性相位转和我记得的方式
that in the continuous-time case we had a similar situation namely that a
在连续时间的情况下，我们有一个类似的情况，即，一个
timeshare
分时度假
corresponded to a linear phase
对应于一个线性相位
there also is a dual to the time shifting property
也有是双的时移特性
which is referred to as the frequency shifting property
这被称为频移特性
which tells us dead if we
它告诉我们死了，如果我们
multiply a time function by a complex exponential
通过一个复杂的指数乘以一个时间函数
that in effect generates
在效果产生
a frequency share and will see this frequency shifting property
频率共享和会看到这个频移特性
surface in a slightly different way shortly
一个稍微不同的方式浮现在不久
when we talk about the modulation property in the discrete-time case
当我们谈论在离散时间情况下，调制特性
another important property that will want to make you so
该会希望你这样的另一个重要属性
shortly is Lenny arity which follows in a very straightforward way from
不久是莱尼元数它遵循一个非常简单的方法从
the Fourier transform definition
傅里叶变换的定义
and the linearity property says simply
和线性度性能说的简单
that the 48 transform of Assam
该48变换阿萨姆
or linear combination is the same with your combination the Fourier transforms
或线性组合是相同的与组合的傅立叶变换
again that's a property that we saw in continuous-time
再次，这是一个我们在连续时间看到属性
and also among other properties
还除其他性质
there is a parser balls relation for the discrete-time case
有对离散时间情况下的解析器球关系
then in effect says something similar to continuous-time
那么实际上是说类似于连续时间的东西
specifically dead the energy E
特别是死者的能量E
in the sequence is proportional
序列中的正比
to the energy E in the 48 transform
在48变换的能量E
the energy over one period or said another way
能量在一个周期或者说另一种方式
in fact or another way that it can be said is
事实上或另一种方式，也可以说是
that the energy in the time domain is proportional to the power
在时域中的能量正比于功率
in his periodic for a transport
在他的周期为一个传输
okay so these are some other properties
好了，这些都是一些其他属性
in and are the as i indicated parallel somewhat properties that we saw in
的，并且是我们在看到了正如我有点并行性能
continuous-time
连续时间
two additional properties their will play important roles
两个额外的属性其将发挥重要作用
indiscreet I'm just as they did in continuous-time
指手画脚，我只是因为他们在连续时间做
are the convolution property and the modulation property
是卷积特性和调制特性
the convolution property is the property that tells us
卷积属性是告诉我们的物业
how to relate the Fourier transform
如何与傅里叶变换
all the convolution two sequences
所有的卷积两个序列
to the Fourier transforms of the individual sequences
到各个序列的傅立叶变换
and not surprisingly what happens and this can be
并没有发生什么令人惊讶的，这可能是
demonstrated algebraically not surprisingly
证明代数不出奇
the four EA transform above the convolution
四EA变换的卷积以上
is simply the product of the Fourier transforms
简直是傅立叶变换的产品
so Fourier transform maps
所以傅立叶变换图
convolution in the time domain the multiplication in the frequency domain
卷积的时域频域的乘法
now convolutional courses arises in the context of linear time-invariant systems
现在卷积课程中出现的线性时不变系统的情况下
in particular if we have a system with an impulse response a true fan
特别是如果我们有一个系统的脉冲响应一个真正的球迷
input excessive and the output is the convolution
输入过大的输出是卷积
the convolution property then tells us dead
卷积属性则告诉我们死
in the frequency domain for EA transform
在对EA变换频域
is the product love the Fourier transform
是产品爱傅立叶变换
the impulse response and the forty a transformer the input
的脉冲响应和40的变压器的输入
now we also saw
现在我们也看到了
and have talked about a relationship between
和刚才讲的关系
the Fourier transform the impulse response and what we called
傅立叶变换的脉冲响应和此谓
the frequency response
的频率响应
in the context love the response to the system
在上下文爱响应系统
to a complex exponential specifically
到复指数具体
complex exponentials are I can functions have linear time-invariant systems
复指数是我能函数具有线性时不变系统
wanna be's into the system gives us as an output
想成为的进入系统给了我们作为一个输出
a complex exponential with the same complex frequency
复指数具有相同的复杂频率
multiplied by what you referred to as the eye can value
乘以你所提到的眼睛能重视
and as you saw in the
正如你在看
video course manual this I can value this constant multiplier
视频课程手册这样我可以珍惜这个常数乘法器
on the exponential is in fact
上的指数是实际上
the 48 transform up the impulse response
48变换向上的脉冲响应
evaluated at that frequency
在该频率计算
now we saw exactly the same statement
现在我们看到了一模一样的声明
in continuous-time and in fact we use
在连续时间，事实上，我们使用
that statement the frequency response interpretation
该语句的频率响应解释
love the 48 trance for the impulse response
爱48恍惚的脉冲响应
we use that to motivate and intuitive interpretation
我们用它来激励和直观的解释
of the convolution property now formally the convolution property can be
卷积物业现正式卷积属性可以是
developed by
由开发
taking the convolution some applying the Fourier transforms into it
服用一些应用傅立叶卷积转换成它
doing the appropriate substitution variables in a changing order summations
做在不断变化的顺序求和适当的替代变量
Center in all the algebra
中心在所有的代数
works out to show that it's a product but as I stressed
工程以表明它是一个产品，但我强调
when we discussed this with continuous time the interpretation the underlying
当我们讨论这与连续时间解释相关
interpretation
解释
is particularly important to understand so let me review it again
尤为重要的是了解，所以让我再作检讨的
in the discrete-time case and it's exactly the same
在离散时间情况下，它是完全相同的
for discrete-time for continuous-time
对于离散时间的连续时间
specifically the argument was that the Fourier transform
具体的说法是，傅立叶变换
all a sequence or signal
所有的序列或信号
corresponds to decomposing it into a linear combination of complex
对应于分解成复杂的线性组合
exponentials
指数函数
what the airport to those complex exponentials its
什么是机场到那些复杂的指数函数及其
basically proportional to the four EA transport
基本上正比于4 EA运输
if we think a pushing through the system that linear combination
如果我们认为推动通过线性组合系统
then each love those complex exponentials
那么每个爱那些复杂的指数函数
gets the airport to modified are multiplied
得到机场到修改的相乘
by the Fourier transform all up by the frequency response
由傅立叶的频率响应变换了一切
which we saw is the Fourier transform love the impulse response
我们看到的是傅立叶变换爱的脉冲响应
so the airport to up the output complex exponentials
所以到机场了输出复指数
is then the amplitudes of the input complex exponentials
是输入复指数的则振幅
multiplied by the frequency response
乘以频率响应
and the Fourier transform the output in effect
和傅立叶变换的效果的输出
is an expression its expressing the summation
它是表达的求和表达式
or integration of the output as a linear combination of all of these exponentials
或集成的输出，因为所有这些指数函数的线性组合
with the appropriate complex amplitudes
用适当的复振幅
so its important in thinking about
所以它在思考重要
the convolution property to think about it in terms
卷积财产去想它的条款
a nothing more then the fact that we decompose the input
一个没有那么多的事实，我们分解输入
and we're now modifying separately
而我们现在分别修改
through multiplication scaling
通过乘法缩放
the airport to or each of the complex exponential company
到机场或各复指数公司
now what we saw in continuous time is that this interpretation
现在我们在连续时间看到的是，这种解释
and the convolution property
和卷积性质
lead to an important concept namely the concept the filtering
导致一个重要的概念，即概念的过滤
kind of the idea that if we decompose the input as a linear combination of
样的想法，如果我们分解输入为的线性组合
complex exponentials
复指数
we can separately attenuator amplify
我们可以分别衰减器放大
each of those compounds and in fact
每个这些化合物和实际上
we could exactly pass some center frequencies and totally eliminate other
我们可以准确地传递一些中心频率和完全消除其他
center frequencies
中心频率
so again just as in continuous-time
所以再次正如在连续时间
we can talk about an ideal filter
我们可以谈论一个理想的滤波器
and what I show here is the frequency response
而我在这里展示的是频率响应
love idea low-pass filter
爱情的想法低通滤波器
the idea low-pass filter of course passes
当然，这个想法低通滤波器通过
exactly with a gain of one
正好与1的增益
frequencies around zero and eliminates
在零附近的频率和消除
totally other frequencies
完全其它频率
however an important distinction here between continuous-time and
然而一个重要的区别这里连续时间之间
discrete-time
离散时间
is the fact that whereas in continuous time when we talked about an ideal
是，而在连续的时间，当我们谈到一个理想的事实
filter
过滤器
we passed a band of frequencies and totally eliminate everything else out to
我们通过一个频带，并完全消除一切到
infinity
无穷大
in a discrete-time case the frequency response
在离散时间情况下的频率响应
is periodic so obviously
是周期性的如此明显
the frequency response must periodically repeat
频率响应必须周期性地重复
the low low-pass filter and in fact we see that here
低的低通滤波器，实际上我们可以看到，在这里
if we look at the low-pass filter
如果我们看一下低通滤波器
then we've eliminated some frequencies
那么我们已经消除了某些频率
but then we passive course frequencies
但后来我们被动当然频率
around to pie and also frequencies
周围的馅饼和频率也
around minus 25 for that matter around any multiple
在零下25为此事周围的任何倍数
to pie although it's important to recognize
到馅饼虽然它承认很重要
that because of the inherent periodicity at the complex exponentials
因为在复指数的内在周期性
these frequencies are exactly the same frequencies
这些频率是完全相同的频率
as these frequencies so
因为这些频率等等
its low-pass filtering interpreted in terms of frequencies over a range
其低通滤波的范围内解释在频率方面
from minus buy the pie
从零下买饼
well just as we talk about a low-pass filter we can also talk about
还有，正如我们谈论一个低通滤波器，我们也可以谈论
a high pass filter and a high pass filter course with
一个高通滤波器和一个高通滤波器过程中与
past high frequencies
过去的高频率
in a continuous-time case high frequencies man frequencies that
在连续时间的情况下的高频人频率的
go out to infinity in the discrete-time case
出去到无穷大的离散时间情况
course the highest frequencies we can generate our frequencies up the pie
当然，最高的频率，我们可以生成我们的频率高达馅饼
and wants are complex exponentials go past pie
并希望被复指数走过去馅饼
then in fact we start seeing the lower frequencies again might be
那么其实我们开始再次看到更低的频率可能是
indicate what I mean if we think
表明了我的意思，如果我们认为
in the context of the low-pass filter these are low frequencies
在低通滤波器的情况下这些都是低频
as we move along the frequency axis these become high frequencies
当我们沿着频率轴移动这些成为高频率
and as we move further along the frequency axis
和我们再进一步沿着频率轴
what we'll see when we get to for example frequency
我们会看到，当我们到达例如频率
to pie are the same low frequencies
以饼都是一样的低频率
that we see around zero a particular then
我们看到在零附近某则
a and i do. high pass filter in the discrete-time case
一个和我做。在离散时间情况下的高通滤波器
would be a filter that eliminates these frequencies
将消除这些频率的滤波器
and passes frequencies around pie
并绕过馅饼频率
okay so and we've seen the
好了，我们已经看到了
convolution property and its interpretation in terms of filtering
卷积性质及其解释在过滤方面
more broadly the convolution property in combination
更广泛地结合卷积财产
with a number of the other properties today introduced in particular the time
与一些其他属性今天特别引入的时间
shifting and when the arity property
移和时元数属性
allows us to generator analyzes
让我们到发电机的分析
the an ally systems that are described by linear constant coefficient
是由线性常系数描述的盟友系统
difference equations
差分方程
and this again pareles very strongly
而这又pareles非常强烈
the discussion that we carried out in the continuous-time
我们进行了在连续时间的讨论
case their particular let's
他们的情况下，特别是让我们
think I love a discrete-time system
我觉得爱一个离散时间系统
there is described by when your car is the coefficient difference equation
有被当你的车是系数差分方程描述
and will restrict the initial conditions on the equation
并且将限制的初始条件的方程
such that it corresponds to linear time-invariant system
以使得它对应于线性时不变系统
and recall that in fact in our discussion
并记得，其实在我们的讨论
when your constant coefficient difference equations
当你常系数差分方程
is the condition of initial rest
是的初始静止状态
there on the equation that guarantees
上，保证方程有
4s that the system will be causal linear and time-invariant
4秒，该系统将是因果线性时不变
okay now let's consider
好吧，现在让我们考虑
a first-order difference equation system described by first-order difference
由一阶差分描述的一阶差分方程系统
equation and we've talked about the solution of this equation before
方程和我们以前谈过这个方程的解
essentially we run the solution recur simply
本质上，我们运行该解决方案简单地重演
let's now consider generating the solution by
现在让我们考虑通过生成的解决方案
taking advantage the properties the forty a transport
趁着性质四十运输
well just as we did in continuous time we can consider
也正如我们在连续时间做了就可以考虑
applying to 48 transformed to both sides of this equation
施加到48变换与这个方程的两边
and the Fourier transform are why I have been
和傅里叶变换是为什么我一直
courses y Omega and then using the shifting
课程Ÿ欧米茄，然后使用偏移
property the time shifting property the Fourier transform why event -1
财产时移特性的傅立叶变换，为什么事件-1
is y Omega multiplied by
设为y欧米茄乘以
you to the minus jail make and so we have this
你到零下监狱做，所以我们有这个
using the when the arity property we can carry down the scale factor in and these
使用时的参数数量属性，我们可以扛下来的比例因子在这些
two together as they read it here
两者结合起来，因为他们读在这里
and forty a transformer victim and is XO make
四十变压器受害者，是XO化妆
well Wii console this equation
以及Wii游戏机这个方程
the Fourier transform of the output in terms of the Fourier transform
在傅立叶变换的计算的傅立叶变换的输出
up the input and a
构成输入和一个
inappropriate complex scale factor and simply solving this
不合适的复杂规模因素和根本解决这一
for y Omega yields what we have here
y的欧米茄产生我们这里
now what we've used in going from this point to this point
现在我们从这个点到这点用过
is both the shifting property
是两个换档属性
and we've also used the linearity property
而且我们还使用了线性特性
at this point we can recognize that
在这一点上，我们可以承认，
here the Fourier transform the output is the product
此处傅里叶变换的输出是产品
the Fourier transform of the input and
傅立叶变换的输入和
some complex function and from the convolution property
一些复杂的功能，并从卷积属性
then that complex function must in fact
那么实际上，复杂的函数必须
correspond to the frequency response
对应的频率响应
or acquittal atlee the 48 transform
或无罪阿特利48变换
love the impulse response so if we wanted to determine the Fourier
爱的脉冲响应，所以如果我们想确定傅立叶
transform
改造
or the or where the impulse response to the system
或或其中的系统的脉冲响应
let's say for example then it becomes a matter
比方说，例如它就会变成一个问题
love having identified the 4e a transformer the impulse response which
爱在确定的4E变压器的脉冲响应的
is the frequency response
是频率响应
we now want to inverse transform to get the impulse response
我们现在要进行反变换得到的脉冲响应
well how do we inverse transform of course we could do it by attempting to
以及我们如何当然逆变换，我们可以通过尝试做
go through the synthesis equation
经过合成公式
for the Fourier transform or we can do is we did
对于傅里叶变换，或者我们可以做的就是我们所做的
in a continuous-time case which is to take advantage
在连续时间的情况下这是利用
I love what we know and in particular
我爱我们所知道的，尤其是
we know dead from an example that we work before
我们知道死者从我们以前成功的例子
this is in fact the 48 transform
这实际上是在48变换
all a sequence which is
所有的序列是
a to the N times
一到N次
you then and so in essence by inspection
你再等在本质上通过检验
very similar to what has going on can
非常相似，有什么事情可以
in continuous-time essentially by inspection
在连续时间基本上是通过检查
we can then solve for the impulse response to the system
然后我们可以解决该系统的脉冲响应
okay so that procedure follows very much
还好，这样的程序如下十分
the kind of procedure that we've carried out in continuous-time
我们已经在连续时间进行的一种程序
and this is the course is discussed in more detail
这就是过程进行更详细的讨论
in the text well let's
在文中也让我们
a look at that example
看看这个例子
then here we have the impulse response
那么在这里我们有脉冲响应
for that for associated with the system described by that particular
对于与由该特定描述的系统相关联的
difference equation and to the right of that
差分方程，并以该权利
we have the Associated frequency response
我们有相关的频率响应
and one other things that we notice and this is drawn for a
而且我们注意到一个其他的东西，这是绘制一个
positive between 0&1 what we noticed in fact is that
介于0和1是什么，我们注意到其实值得肯定的是
it is an approximation to
它是一个近似
a low-pass filter because it tends to attenuate
一个低通滤波器，因为它往往会削弱
the high frequencies and retain and in fact
高频率和保留，事实上
amplify the low-frequency now
现在放大低频
if instead actually the impulse response
如果不是实际的脉冲响应
was such that we picked a to be negative between minus 10
就是这样，我们选择了一个为负零下10之间
and the impulse response in the time domain looks like this
和在时域中的脉冲响应是这样的
and the corresponding frequency response
和相应的频率响应
looks like this and that becomes an approximation
看起来是这样的，并且成为一个近似值
to a high pass filter
到一个高通滤波器
so in fact a first-order difference equation
所以其实一阶差分方程
as we see has a frequency response depending on the value obey
因为我们看到有根据值服从的频率响应
dad either looks approximately like a low-pass filter for a positive or a high
爸要么看起来大约像一个低通滤波器，用于正的或高的
pass filter for a negative
低通滤波器为一负
very much like the first order differential equation
非常喜欢的一阶微分方程
looked like a low-pass filter in the continuous-time
看起来像在连续时间低通滤波器
case and in fact I'd like to illustrate
区分，事实上我想说明
is the filtering characteristics
是的滤波特性
for example love filtering using first-order difference equation
比如喜欢用一阶差分方程滤波
and the example that a lil astray
和例子，一个可爱的小误入歧途
is filtering over sequence that in fact is filtered very often
被过滤过的序列，其实是过滤经常
for a very practical reasons namely a sequence which represents the Dow Jones
对于一个非常实际的原因，即一个序列，该序列代表道琼斯
Industrial Average
工业平均
over a fairly long period and
在一个相当长的时期，
will process the Dow Jones Industrial Average first
首先会处理道琼斯工业平均指数
through first-order difference equation where if we begin
通过在那里，如果我们开始的一阶差分方程
with a sequel 0 then referring to the frequency response
与续集0，则指的是频率响应
that we have here equal 0 would simply be
我们在这里等于0，简直是
passing all frequencies as a as positive
通过所有频率为为阳性
we start to retain mostly low frequencies
我们先来留住大部分是低频率
and the larger a gets but still less than 1
和较大的一个变，但仍小于1
the more it attenuates high frequencies at the expensive low frequencies
越衰减高频在昂贵的低频率
so let's watch the filtering first
让我们先看过滤
with a positive and we'll see if behave as a low pass filter and then
以积极的，我们会看到，如果表现为一个低通滤波器，然后
with a negative and we'll see
带有负，我们会看到
the difference equation behaving as a high pass filter
差分方程表现为一个高通滤波器
what we see here is the Dow Jones Industrial Average over
我们在这里看到的是道琼斯工业平均指数比
roughly a five year period from 1927 to 1930 to
大约五年期间1927年至1930年，以
and in fact that big dip in the middle
而实际上，在中间大倾角
is the famous stock market crash of 1929
是1929年的著名股灾
and we can see that following that in fact the market continued
我们可以看到，下面的，事实上，市场持续
a very long downward trend and
一个很长的下降趋势，
what we now want to do is process this
我们现在想要做的就是这个过程
through a difference equation
通过差分方程
above the Dow Jones average we show the impulse response to the difference
上面的道琼斯平均，我们表明该差值的脉冲响应
equation here
这里方程
we've chosen the parameter a equal to 0
我们选择的参数等于0
and the impulse response will be displayed on
和脉冲响应将被显示在
in expanded scale in relation to
在有关扩大规模
the scale love the input and for that matter the scale of the output
规模喜欢的输入和为此事输出规模
now with the impulse response shown here which is just an impulse
现在在这里它示出的脉冲响应是只是一个脉冲
in fact the output shown on the bottom trace
其实在底部走线所示的输出
is exactly identical to the input
是完全相同的输入
and what will want to do now is increase
什么会想现在要做的就是增加
first the parameter a and the impulse response
第一参数a和脉冲响应
will begin to look like an exponential
将开始看起来像一个指数
with a duration: that's longer and longer as
与时间：这是越来越长的
a moves from 0 to 1
从0移动到1
correspondingly we will get more and more low pass filtering as the
相应地，我们将获得越来越多的低通滤波的
coefficient a
系数a
increases from 0 toward one so now
增加了从0往一所以现在
we are increasing the parameter a we see that
我们增加了一个参数，我们可以看到，
the bottom trace in relation to the middle trace in fact is
相对于中间迹实际上底部迹线是
looking more and more smooth or
看起来越来越光滑或
low-pass filtered and here now we have
低通滤波，在这里我们现在有
a fair amount of smoothing to the point where the stock market crash of 1929
平滑的地步了相当数量，其中1929年的股市崩盘
is totally lost in fact I'm sure there are many people who
其实是完全失去我敢肯定有很多人谁
wish that through filtering we could in fact have avoided the stock market crash
希望通过筛选，我们实际上可能已经避免了股市大跌
altogether
共
now let's decrease
现在让我们减少
a from one back toward zero
从一个走回零
and as we do that we will be taking out
当我们这样做，我们将取出
the low-pass filtering and when they finally reaches
低通滤波和当他们终于到达
0 the impulse response to the filter will again
0到滤波器的脉冲响应将再次
be in in polls and so the output will be
在调查中，所以输出将是
once again identical to the input
再次与输入相同
and that's where we are now
而这也正是我们现在
right now we want to continue to decrease
现在我们要继续减少
a so that it becomes negative moving
一，使之成为负移动
from zero toward -1 and what we will see in that case
从零走向-1，我们在这种情况下，会看到
is more and more high-pass filtering
越来越高通滤波
on the output in relation to the input
上在相对于输入输出
and this will be particularly evident in again
并且这将是特别明显的再
the region a pipe frequencies represented by sharp transitions which
该地区由夏普为代表的过渡管道的频率
of course
当然
the market crash goodnight 1929 would represent
市场大跌晚安1929年会代表
so here now a is decreasing
所以这里现在正在减少
toward -1 we see that the high frequencies
朝-1我们看到高频率
or rapid variations are emphasize
或迅速变化是强调
and finally let's move from -1
最后，让我们从移动-1
back toward zero taking out the high-pass filtering
背面朝向零取出的高通滤波
and ending up with
并结束与
equal to 0 corresponding to an impulse response which is an impulse
等于0对应于它是一个脉冲的脉冲响应
in other words and identity system and let me stress once again that
在其他单词和识别系统，让我再一次强调，
the time scale on which we displayed the impulse response
上，我们显示的脉冲响应的时间尺度
is an expanded time scale in relation to the timescale
是一个扩展的时间刻度相对于时间刻度
on which we displayed the input and the output
上，我们显示的输入和输出
okay so we see that in fact a
好了，所以我们看到，其实是一个
first-order difference equation is
一阶差分方程为
a filter and in fact it's a very important class the filters and its use
一个过滤器，实际上它是一个非常重要的一类过滤器及其使用
very often to do
很多时候做
approximate low-paying some high-pass filtering
近似​​低薪一些高通滤波
now in addition to
现在除了
the convolution property another
卷积属性的另一个
important property that we had in continuous-time and that we have in
我们曾在连续时间的，我们有重要的属性
discrete-time
离散时间
is the modulation property the modulation property tells us
是调制特性调制特性告诉我们
what happens in the frequency domain when
在频域上发生的事情时，
you multiply signals in the time domain
你在时域中乘以信号
in continuous-time the modulation property corresponded to the statement
在连续时间调制属性对应于表
that if we multiply in the time domain
如果我们乘以在时域
we convolved the 48 transforms
我们的卷积变换48
in the frequency domain and in discrete-time
在频域中和在离散时间
we have very much the same
我们有很多相同的
kinda relationship
有点关系
the only real distinction between the
之间的唯一真正的区别
is is that in the discrete-time case
是的，在离散时间情况
in carrying out the convolution its integration
在开展卷积其整合
only over a two-party interval and
只有在两方的时间间隔和
what that corresponds to is what's referred to as
什么对应的是什么的简称
a periodic convolution
以周期卷积
as opposed to the continuous-time case
相对于连续时间情况
where what we have is a convolution
在那里我们所拥有的是一个卷积
that is a periodic on pollution
这是一个周期上的污染
so again we have a convolution property in discrete-time
所以我们再次在离散时间卷积性质
that is very much like the convolution property in continuous-time
这非常类似于在连续时间的卷积特性
the only real difference is that here work involving
唯一真正的区别是，这里涉及的工作
periodic functions and so
周期函数等
its a periodic convolution which involves integration only over to pie
它的一个周期卷积涉及整合只能交给馅饼
and herbal
和草药
rather than in immigration from minus infinity the question
而不是从负无穷移民问题
well let's and take a look at the
那么让我们来看一看在
example love the modulation property which will then
例如爱的调制特性它在将
leave to one particular application and a very useful application
离开一个特定的应用程序和一个非常有用的应用
love the modulation property in discrete-time
爱在离散时间调制特性
example that I 12 pic is
例如，我12 PIC是
example in which we consider modulating a signal
在此示例中，我们考虑调制信号
with a signal with another signal
与另一信号的信号
X evander x1 event as i indicated
正如我X霍利X1事件
here which is -1 to the end
这里是-1到端
essentially with that says is that
本质上，说的是，
any signal which I modulate with this effect corresponds to taking the
我与调节这种影响任何信号对应于服用
original signal
原始信号
and then going through that signal alternating
然后将通过该信号交替
the algebraic sign
代数符号
now we in in applying the modulation property of course
现在我们在应用过程中的调制特性
what we need to do is develop the 48 transform
我们需要做的是开发48变换
this signal this signal which I
这个信号此信号，我
rewrite I can ride either is -1 to the air to rewrite is you DJ pie and since
重写我可以骑要么是-1到空气中重写被你DJ馅饼和自
you the J pie
您歼馅饼
is equal to -1 is a periodic signal
是等于-1是一个周期性的信号
and if the periodic signal that I show here
如果周期信号，我在这里展示
and recall that to get the 48 transform other periodic signal
并记得拿到48变换其他周期性信号
one way to do it is to
做到这一点的一种方法是
generate the forty a series coefficients for the periodic signal
生成40的周期信号的一系列系数
and then identify the Fourier transform as an impulse train
然后找出傅立叶变换为脉冲串
where the heights of the impulses in the impulse train
凡在列车冲动冲动的高度
are proportional the proportionality factor to pry
是成正比的比例系数撬
proportional 240 a series coefficients
240系列的系数成正比
so let's first workout what the for a series is it for this example
所以让我们先锻炼一下了一系列它是在这个例子
in fact it's fairly easy here is
其实这也很容易在这里
the general synthesis equation for
对于一般合成方程
the forty a series and
第四十一个系列
if we take our particular example
如果我们把我们的特殊的例子
where if we look back at the curve above
在那里，如果我们回头看看上面的曲线
what we recognize is that the period
我们认识那是什么时期
is equal to 2 merely repeat after two points
在后两个点等于2只重复
then capital in is equal to two
那么资本等于两个
and so we can just write this out with the two turns
所以我们可以只写这一点与两圈
and the two terms involved are x1 a van is a0
而且这两个术语X1一辆面包车为A0
0 go fishin as cake 0
0去钓鱼蛋糕0
in a1 and this is with
在A1，这是与
cake was one we substituted in capital an equal to two
蛋糕是一个大家取代资本平等的两个
right well we can do a little bit about to bring here obviously
右好，我们可以做一点点地在这里带来明显
cross of the factors to and what we recognize
的因素穿越到什么，我们承认
if we compare this expression with
如果我们这个表达式与比较
the original signal which is you the j-pop I N
这是你的J-pop的I N的原始信号
then we can simply identify the fact dead
那么我们可以简单地识别的事实死
80 0 coefficient is zero that's the DC term
80 0系数为零那是直流项
and call fish in a1 is equal to 1
和a1中称之为鱼等于1
so we've done it simply by essentially
所以我们基本上是由它完成的简单
inspecting the for EA
检查对EA
series synthesis equation
系列合成公式
okay now if we want to get the Fourier transform for this we take those
现在没事了，如果我们想要得到的傅里叶变换，为此我们采取这些
coefficients
系数
an essentially generate
基本上产生
an impulse train where we
一个冲动的火车，我们
chooses values for the impulses to pie
选择值的冲动派
times the forty a series coefficients
倍的40一系列系数
so before a series coefficients array0 sequel to zero in a one is equal to 1
如此前的一系列系数ARRAY0续集零在一等于1
so noticed that in
所以注意到，在
the plot that I shown here above the 40 a transform
我这里显示的40变换上述情节
love x1 a band we have the zeroth coefficient which happens to be 0
爱X1带我们第零系数恰好是0
and so I haven't indicated impose
所以我没有强加表示
there we have the
还有，我们有
coefficient a one and the coefficient a1
系数A 1与系数a1
occurs at a frequency which is
发生的频率为
Omega 0 and Omega 0 in fact is equal to hi
欧米茄0和Omega 0实际上等于喜
because the signal is the the j-pop I N
因为信号是一些J-Pop I N
well in what's this impulse over here
以及在什么这种冲动在这里
well any polls is ace
以及任何调查是王牌
corresponds to the four-day series go fishin a sieve -1
对应于为期四天的系列去钓鱼筛子-1
and of course if we drew this out
当然，如果我们画了这一点
over a longer frequency axis we would see lots of other impulses
在一个较长的频率轴上，我们会看到很多其他的冲动
because it the fact that the four th transform periodically repeats
因为这一个事实，即4个变换周期性重复
or equipment leader for a series coefficients periodically
或设备的领导者定期一系列系数
p so this is the coefficient
p之间，这样，这是系数
80 this is the coefficient
80这是系数
a one with a factor to pie this is 25 times a zero
一个具有一个因素馅饼这是25次零
and two pi times they won
和两个PI时候，他们赢了
and then this is simply an indication
然后这仅仅是一个指示
that is periodically repeated
被周期性地重复
right now let's consider what happens if we take a signal
现在让我们考虑，如果我们采取一个信号发生了什么
and multiplier modulated by
和乘法器调制
-1 to the end well in the frequency domain
-1至末尾以及在频域
that corresponds to a convolution
对应于卷积
let's consider a signal x2 a van
让我们考虑一个信号X2一辆面包车
which has a $4 EA transform as i've indicated here
其中有4美元的EA变换，因为我已经在这里表示
then the Fourier transform the product
然后傅里叶变换的乘积
affects 1 event next to %uh van is the convolution
影响旁边％1事件呃面包车是卷积
up these two spectra and
了这两个光谱和
recall that if you can fall something
记得，如果你能掉下东西
with an impulse train is this is that simply corresponds to taking the
有一种冲动列车，这是简单地对应于服用
something
某物
and placing it at the positions love
并把它的位置爱
should the impulses so in fact
如若如此冲动，其实
the result the convolution this with this
该结果与此卷积这
would then be the spectrum their I indicate here
然后将频谱他们我在此说明
namely this spectrum shifted up to pie
即此谱移来的馅饼
and of course two-minus by and then
当然还有两减去，然后
of course to not only Piper three pie in five
当然，不仅派3派五
by et cetera et cetera and
村庄，等等等等，并
so this spectrum finally corresponds to
所以这个频谱终于对应
the Fourier transform -1 to the end
傅立叶变换-1到端
times X to have an where x2 event is the sequence
多次X有一个地方X2事件序列
spectrum was x2 make
谱X2化妆
okay now this is in fact important
现在没事了其实这是重要的
useful and interesting point what it says is
有用和有趣的一点是什么它说的是
I have a signal with a certain spectrum and if I
我有一个信号具有一定的频谱，如果我
modulate multiply that signaled by -1 to the end
乘法调制信号是由-1到年底
meeting that I alternate the signs then
会议认为我交替指示牌，然后
it takes the low frequencies in effect the ship's the spectrum by pie
它需要有效的低频船舶的频谱由馅饼
so it takes the low frequencies and moves them up the high frequencies
所以它需要的低频率和移动它们的高频率
and will incidently take the high frequencies and movement the low
并顺便说一句采取高频率和运动的低
frequency
频率
so in fact we in essence saw this when we
所以实际上我们在本质上看见了这个，当我们
so or twenty talked about the example love
因此，二十谈过恋爱的例子
a sequence which was aided the end times you have an
一个序列是援建结束时间你有一个
notice let me draw your attention to the fact dead
注意让我提请你注意这样的事实：死人
when a is positive we have
当a是正我们
this sequence and its Fourier transform
这个序列及其傅立叶变换
is as II show on the right
是为第二显示在右侧
for a negative
对于负
the sequence is
该序列是
the identical to a positive but with alternating signs
在相同的一个积极的，但有迹象交替
and the Fourier transform it that you can now see
和傅里叶变换它，你现在可以看到
and verify also algebraically
同时也验证代数
if you'd like is identical to this spectrum
如果你想是一样的这个频谱
simply shifted by pie
只需馅饼转移
so it says in fact that multiplying
所以说，在事实相乘
that impulse response or if we think I've a positive and a negative
该脉冲响应，或者如果我们认为我有一个正的和负
that is algebraically similar to multiplying
这是代数类似相乘
the impulse response by -1 to the end and in the frequency domain
由-1到端和在频域中的脉冲响应
the affected that essentially is shifting the spectrum by pie
受影响的，基本上是由饼转移谱
we can interpret that in the context that the modulation property
我们可以理解，在上下文中，调制特性
now it's interesting that
现在有趣的是，
what that says is there
什么，说是有
if we have system which corresponds to
如果我们有系统，其对应于
a low-pass filter as i indicated here
一个低通滤波器，正如我在这里
with an impulse response a true fan
用脉冲响应一个真正的球迷
and its it can be any approximation to a low pass filter and even an idea Lopez
并且其也可以是任何近似到低通滤波器，甚至一个想法洛佩兹
filter
过滤器
if we want to convert that to a high pass filter
如果我们想将其转换成一个高通滤波器
we can't do that by generating a new system
我们不能这样做，产生一个新的系统
whose impulse response is -1 to the end
其脉冲响应是-1到端
times the impulse response the low-pass filter
倍的脉冲响应低通滤波器
and this modulation
与该调制
by -1 to the end will take the frequency response
由-1到年底将采取频率响应
this system and shifted by popeye
这个系统和转向大力水手
so that what's going on here at low frequencies
所以说这是怎么回事就在低频
will now go on here at high frequency
现在将继续在这里高频
this also says incidently dead if
这也是说，顺便说一句，如果死
we look at
我们来看看
the a and idea low-pass filter and i do. high pass filter
的一个想法和低通滤波器和我做。高通滤波器
and we choose the cutoff frequencies for comparison
我们选择了截止频率进行比较
for the band with the filter to be equal
用于与过滤器的频带为等于
since this ideal high pass filter is
因为这个理想高通滤波器
this idea low-pass filter with the frequency response shifted
这个主意的低通滤波器的频率响应偏移
by popeye the modulation property tells us
通过大力水手的调制特性告诉我们
that in the time domain with that corresponds to
在与对应于该时域
is an impulse response multiplied five minus one to the S
时的脉冲响应乘以5减去1到S
so it says that the impulse response
所以说，脉冲响应
love the high-pass filter or quently the inverse Fourier transform
爱的高通滤波器或quently傅立叶逆变换
love a high pass filter frequency response
爱一个高通滤波器的频率响应
is -1 to the end times the
是-1到结束时间的
impulse response to the low-pass filter that all follows for the modulation
到低通滤波器，所有如下的调制脉冲响应
property
属性
now there's another way interesting and useful way
现在有另一种方式有趣和有用的方式
that modulation can be used to
该调制可以用于
implement or convert from low pass filtering the high-pass filtering
实施或由低通滤波，高通滤波转换
the modulation property tells us about multiplying the time domain is shifting
调制特性告诉我们乘以时域移
in the frequency domain
在频域
and the example that we happen to pick said if you multiply
而且我们发生的例子来接说，如果你乘
or modulate by -1 to the end that takes low frequencies and ship them to
或-1调节到去年底，采用低频率，并将它们运送到
high-frequency
高频
what that tells us it as a practical and useful
什么，告诉我们它作为一种实用和有用的
notion is the following suppose we have a system
概念是下列假设我们有一个系统
that we know is a low pass filter and it's a good luck this
我们知道是一个低通滤波器，这是一个好运气这
how might we use it as a high pass filter
怎么可能，我们把它作为一个高通滤波器
well one way to do it instead of shifting its frequency response
还有一种方式做，而不是改变其频率响应它
is to take the original signal
是取原始信号
shift its low frequencies the high frequencies and its high frequencies the
改变其低频率的高频率和它的高频率的
low frequencies
低频
by multiplying the input signal the original signal by -1 to the yen
乘以输入由-1信号的原始信号，以日元
process that with the low-pass filter we're now with sitting at the low
处理，与低通滤波器，我们现在正在与坐在低
frequencies with a high frequencies
频率的高频率
and then unscramble it all at the output
然后解读这一切在输出
so that we put the frequencies back where they belong
让我们把频率回属于他们的地方
and I summarize that here let's suppose for example that
我总结的是，这里我们假设的例子，
this system was a low-pass filter in and
这个系统是与一个低通滤波器
so it low pass filters whatever comes into it
所以低通滤波器任何进入它
down below I indicate taking the input and first interchanging
向下跌破我表示接受输入和第一互换
the high and low frequencies through modulation with -1 to the end
通过调制-1到最后的高频和低频
doing a low-pass filtering which and what sitting at the low frequencies here
做一个低通滤波的，什么坐在这里在低频率
with a high frequencies
具有高频率
this signal and then after the low-pass filtering
此信号然后经过低通滤波
moving the frequencies back where they belong
移动频率回到属于他们的地方
by again modulating with -1 to the end
通过再次-1调控进行到底
and that in fact turns out to be a very useful
并且事实上，原来是一个非常有用的
a very useful notion for
对于一个非常有用的概念
applying a fixed low pass filter
施加一个固定的低通滤波器
to do high-pass filtering and vice versa
做高通滤波，反之亦然
okay no
还好没有
what we've seen and what we've talked about
我们所看到的和我们谈过
are the for a representation for
是用于表示一个
discrete-time signals and prior to that
离散时间信号，并在此之前，
continuous-time say and we've seen some very important similarities and
连续时间说，我们已经看到了一些非常重要的相似之处和
differences
差异
and what I'd like to do is conclude
和我想要做的是总结
this lecture by summarizing
本次讲座通过总结
those various relationships kinda ball in one package
这些不同的关系还挺球在一个封装中
and in fact drawing your attention to
而事实上提请你注意
both the similarities and differences and comparisons between
二者的相同点和不同点之间的比较
well let's begin in this summary
好，让我们开始在本概要
by first looking at the continuous-time
首先着眼于连续时间
for a series in a continuous time for a series
对于一个系列中的连续时间系列
we have a periodic time function
我们有一个定期的时间函数
expanded as a linear combination of harmonically related complex
展开如下的谐波相关的复杂的线性组合
exponentials
指数函数
and there are an infinite number these that are required to do the
并且有无限多的这些所需要做的
decomposition
分解
and we saw and analysis equation which tells us
我们看到和分析方程，它告诉我们
how to get these four EA series coefficients
如何让这四个EA系列系数
through an integration on the original time
通过对原时间的积分
and notice in this that what we have
并注意在这一点，我们有什么
is a continuous periodic timer function what we end up with
是一个连续的周期性定时器功能，我们结束了
are in the frequency domain is a sequence a Fourier series coefficients
是在频域上是一个序列的傅立叶级数的系数
which in fact
这实际上
is an infinite sequence namely requires all values
是一个无限序列，即要求所有的值
K in general
K的一般
we had then generalized that to the continuous time for EA transform
我们当时曾概括说来持续时间对EA变换
an ineffective doing that what happened is that
一个无效的这样做，什么事是，
the synthesis equation in the four EA
在4 EA合成方程
series became
系列成为
integral relationship in the Fourier transform
在傅立叶积分变换关系
and we now have a continuous-time
而我们现在有一个连续时间
function which is no longer periodic this was for the a periodic case
函数，它不再是周期性的，这是为一个周期的情况下
represented as a linear combination up infinite has only close and frequency
表示为一个线性组合了无限的只有关闭和频率
complex exponentials with complex amplitudes given by Eq civil make it the
复杂的指数函数与方程给出复振幅民间使其成为
Omega divided by two pi
欧米加除以2圆周
and we had of course the corresponding analysis equation the told us how to get
我们不得不当然相应的分析方程告诉我们怎么走
exe below me here
exe文件下面我在这里
we have a continuous-time function which is a periodic
我们有一个连续时间函数，它是一个周期性的
and a continuous function of frequency
和频率的连续函数
which is a periodic
这是一个周期
the conceptual strategy in a discrete-time case
在离散时间情况下的概念的策略
was very similar with
是具有非常相似
so differences resulting in the
这样的差异导致
relationships because of some inherent differences between
由于存在一些本质上的差异关系
continuous-time and discrete-time we had
连续时间和离散时间我们有
we began with the discrete-time for you series
我们开始与离散时间为您系列
corresponding to representing a periodic sequence
对应于表示一个周期序列
through a set of complex exponentials
通过一组复指数
where now we only required a finite number of the
在那里，现在我们只需要的数量有限
is because the fact that in fact with there are only a finite number of
是因为这一事实实际上与只有有限数量的
harmonically related complex exponentials
谐波相关复指数
that's an inherent property discrete-time complex exponentials
这是一个固有的属性离散时间复指数
and so we have a discrete
所以我们有一个离散
periodic type function and we ended up with a set of 48 series coefficients
函数周期类型和我们结束了一套48系列系数
which of course are discrete as for a series coefficients are
这当然是不连续的，作为一系列系数是
and which periodically repeat because it the fact
并且周期性地重复，因为它的事实
that the Associated complex exponentials periodically
该相关复指数定期
repeat we then
重复我们再
used in arguments similar to the continuous-time case
在参数类似于连续时间的情况下使用
for going for periodic time fortunes a periodic time
对于持续了周期时间财富的周期时间
functions and we ended up with a relationship
功能和我们结束了一个关系
describing representation for a periodic
描述表示为一个周期
discrete-time signals in which now
离散时间信号，其中现
the synthesis equation went from a summation to an integration
从求和的合成公式去整合
says the frequencies are now if it hasn't we close
说的频率是现在，如果它没有我们关闭
involving frequencies only over to pry interval
涉及的频率仅在撬区间
and for which the amplitude factor Xa bomb-maker
且其振幅因子Xa炸弹制造者
well the apathy factors X will make it the Omega divided by two pi
好冷漠因素通道x将使其成为欧米茄分为两个圆周率
and this term Mexico may go which is the 48 transform
而这一届墨西哥可能会是在48变换
is given by this some Asian
由下式给出这方面的一些亚洲
and course involves all of the values affects a bit
当然涉及到所有值的影响有点
and so the important difference between the continuous-time and discrete-time
等连续时间和离散时间之间的重要区别
case kinda rose in part to the fact that discrete I miss discrete-time
情况有点上升部分的事实，分立我想念离散时间
continuous-time is continuous time
连续时间是连续的时间
and the fact the complex exponentials a periodic
和事实的复指数函数的周期性
in discrete-time the harmonically related ones periodically repeat
在离散时间的谐波相关的那些周期性地重复
whereas they don't in continuous time
而他们没有在连续的时间
now this among other things has an important consequence for duality
现在这其中包括具有二元性的一个重要后果
and let's go back again and look at this equation
让我们回头再来看这个等式
despair equations clearly their
绝望方程清楚自己的
is no duality between these two equations
是这两个方程之间没有双重性
this involves a summation this involves an integration
这涉及到一个求和这涉及到一个集成
and so in fact if
因此，事实上，如果
we make reference to to our the
我们会参考我们的
their isn't the reality in the continuous-time
其并不现实中的连续时间
for a series however
对于一系列然而
for the continuous-time for EA transform
对于连续时间为EA变换
we're talking about a periodic timer functions in a periodic frequency
我们谈论的周期性频率的周期定时器功能
functions
功能
and in fact we look at these two equations we see very definitely duality
而事实上我们看，我们看的很肯定二重性这两个方程
in other words the time function effectively
换句话说时间函数有效地
is the Fourier transform the four th transport
是傅立叶变换的4个传输
little time reversal in there but basically that's the result
很少有时间逆转在那里，但基本上是这样的结果
and in fact we had exploited that duality property
而事实上，我们已经利用了二元属性
when we talked about the continuous-time for EA transport
当我们谈到的连续时间为EA运输
with the discrete-time Fourier series
用离散时间傅立叶级数
we have a duality
我们有一个对偶
indicated by the fact that we have a periodic time function
的事实，我们有一个定期的时间函数表示
and a sequence which is
和一个序列，该序列是
periodic in the frequency domain and in fact if you look at these two
定期在频域，事实上，如果你看看这两个
expressions
表达式
you see the duality very clearly and so
你看到偶的很清楚，所以
ants the discrete-time Fourier series
蚂蚁的离散时间傅立叶级数
that has to do our D and
有做我们的D和
finally the discrete-time Fourier transform loses the duality
最后的离散时间傅里叶变换失去了对偶
because the fact among other things then in the time domain
因为中间然后其他的东西在时域中的事实
things are inherently discrete whereas in the frequency domain
事物本身是离散的，而在频域
they are inherently continuous so in fact here
他们本质上是连续的所以其实这里
there is no do well
有没有做好
okay now that says that there's a difference in the duality
现在没事了，指出有一个在二元性差异
continuous-time and discrete-time and there's one
连续时间和离散时间和有一个
more very important peace to
更重要的和平
the duality relationship and we can see that
对偶关系，我们可以看到，
first algebraically by comparing
第一代数比较
the continuous-time for a series
连续时间的一系列
and the discrete-time for EA transport
和离散时间为EA运输
the continuous time for a series
持续时间为一个系列